Matthew Cottrell

ClassicCottrell.ca

ClassicCottrell@gmail.com

778-232-4629



About

My name is Matt and I'm a UI/UX designer. I've been in the software industry for 5 years. When I'm not at work, I'm either involved in film production, drawing weird cartoon characters, or reminiscing about my printing days, when I had access to a vinyl plotter, huge screens and endless rolls of paper.

Experience

- 5 years in a start-up environment
- Outgoing & positive personality
- Enthusiastic & dedicated learner
- Adapts easily to new situations & people

- Prepress knowledge & understanding

••00

- I work well independently, however, I love working in a team environment & brainstorming with my colleagues.

Work History		Skills	EXPERIANCE OUT OF
Tagga - Creative Lead UI/UX Lead 2016 - present - User stories, Site mapping, Conception of new platform tools - Creation of Low Fidelity to High Fidelity designs through wireframes, sketches, design, mockups, prototyping (pencil paper, adobe XD) - Software theme & branding, element styles (color exploration, fonts, icons)		UI/UX Design & Coding - HTML, CSS - Foundation, Bootstrap, SASS, LESS - Adobe Experience design - Responsive design - Email template creation - Campaign Monitor & MailChimp - Facebook Ad Manager - Google Adwords	
Lead Design UI/UX - User Experience flow creation - User Interface front-end development - Cross Channel Campaign Strategy - Design & creation of media for campaigns (in-store print design, facebook/ Instagram/twitter social posts, & responsive websites) - Front End Development and QA for site deployments - Social Community Creation - Social posting and storytelling		Art & Design - Adobe Creative suite - Photoshop - Illustrator - InDesign - Video Final Cut & After Effects - Lighting & Set Design - Classical 2D Animation - Stop Motion & Cinemagraphs GIF's	
- Video production C2 Imaging - Sign Maker - Large Format Digital - Lün Cutter Press Op	2000 - 2010 Print Operator	Print & Layout - Sign maker (layout and quality control) - 5 color printing process - T-shirt printing process - Store Front vinyl sign application - Zün (digital die-cutting)	

Education and Training

- Saturn 5 Colour Printing Press Assistant

 BCIT - New Media Design & Web Development Certificate
 2010 - 2011

 Vancouver Film School - Foundation in Film & Design
 2006 - 2007

 Langley Fine Arts School - Fine Arts Major
 2001 - 2004